你好
COLTON OGDEN: Hi.
我叫科尔顿·奥格登 我是这门课的讲师
My name is Colton Ogden, and I am the course instructor
GD50是CS50的游戏开发入门
for GD50, which is CS50's Introduction to Game Development.
CS50之于游戏编程 就像CS50之于通用编程一样
CS50 is to game programming what CS50 is to general-purpose programming
和解决问题的能力 最终成为学生
and problem solving, ultimately a jumping-off point for students
有一点编程经验的人
that might have a little bit of programming experience,
但他们还没有接触过游戏编程
but who haven't necessarily gotten their hands dirty with game programming yet.
GD50采用案例研究方式 每周
GD50 adopts a case study style approach whereby week by week,
我们会看一个特定的博弈 然后分析它
we'll look at a specific game, and we'll analyze it,
弄清楚这些部分是做什么的以及它们是如何形成一个可玩的整体的
figuring out what the parts do and how they form a playable whole.
我们会看看像乒乓球 突破 超级马里奥兄弟 传奇
We'll look at games like Pong, Breakout, Super Mario Bros., Legend
《塞尔达传说》《传送门》等等
of Zelda, Portal, and many more.
在课程的前三个季度
For the first three quarters of the course,
学生将使用Lua和LOVE 2D 一个2D游戏开发框架
students will use Lua and LOVE 2D, a 2D game development framework,
然后在后四分之一过渡到Unity中的C#
and then transition in the latter quarter to C# in Unity,
一个非常流行的现代游戏引擎
a very popular modern game engine.
最终 大量的编程 大量的想法 以及大量的乐趣
Ultimately, lots of programming, lots of ideas, and lots of fun
等待对课程感兴趣的学生
await students interested in the course.
我叫科尔顿·奥格登这是GD50
My name is Colton Ogden, and this is GD50.
[音乐播放]
[MUSIC PLAYING]